100searchengines.com 2015-03-15

# 100 Search Engines - Privacy Statement

We at 100 Search Engines take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy.

**Privacy Policy**  
100 Search Engines respects and protects the privacy of the individuals that use our website. Individually identifiable information about you is **NOT** disclosed to any third party as explained in this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy").

**What Information Do We Collect?**  
100 Search Engines does **NOT** collect any unique information about you (such as your name, email address, ip address, etc.) except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information in the form of an email.

**Cookies**  
When you use 100 Search Engines with a web browser, we will place one or more "cookies" on your machine. We use these cookies to operate 100 Search Engines . You can use your browser settings to remove or block cookies on your computer. 

**With Whom Does 100 Search Engines Share Information?** 100 Search Engines will **NOT** share individually identifiable information about you with any advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. 100 Search Engines may disclose or share non-personal or anonymous or aggregated information with third parties, such as usage statistics of our Services or IP addresses. Aggregated non-personally identifiable information is information recorded about users and collected into groups so that it no longer reflects or references an individually identifiable user. These third parties may collect information when users visit our Services. These third parties may use this aggregated information about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on the other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
The sites displayed as search results or linked to by 100 Search Engines are developed by people over whom 100 Search Engines exercises no control. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information, we do not. 

**Is 100 Search Engines Adware, Spyware or Malware?**  
Absolutely not! 100 Search Engines does **NOT** ; monitor, collect data or 'spy' on its customers. 100 Search Engines is incapable of tracking your overall web use or deciphering anything on your hard drive. 100 Search Engines does **NOT** display pop-up ads or any type of advertising except for paid search results and several affiliate links. All server logs are disabled. We DO NOT distribute any software programs at all (including internet browsers or toolbars). 

**How does 100 Search Engines make any money, if your offer it for free?**  
Some of the search engines listed on the 100 Search Engines website may pay a listing fee or may share revenue from advertising within the search results (sponsored results) as well as affiliate links.

**Use of Remarketing with Google Analytics**  
We collect basic web traffic analysis using Google Analytics to capture information about page visits (showing us which areas of the website are popular and those that are not often visited, this allows us to prioritize our enhancements to our website). This information is anonymous and we use this information only internally - to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Website visitors may opt out of the Google Analytics cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out page. Google has additional information available about their Remarketing Privacy Guidelines, Policies, and Restrictions. 

**Business Transfer**  
If we become involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of our assets, we will provide notice if such a transaction results in your information being subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. You are responsible for periodically reviewing this Privacy Policy for any applicable changes. 

**Questions and/or Suggestions**  
If you have questions and/or suggestions, please Contact Us
